yo nice movies about water food real
quick you guys can watch me order food
I'll see everybody my name is George my
email is George and I must case you be
able to see we got Mosab alright so
whatever want to order guys order garlic
fries whoo I like garlic fries
definitely order some of those what a
weird time no no no no I got I got
something I got to show you guys why
would I want sauce
I don't like sauce oh um so we
definitely wanted some garlic fries I'm
gonna get a burger
yeah lettuce wrap yeah no sauce yeah I
hate sauce all right with good brows hmm
ooh can I get ice cream holy milkshakes
I only get milkshakes ah okay
okay cool
hi guys here's what we're going to talk
about today panda in a box yo is that
hot or what panda Panda panda look it
when you get a panda if you would have
an order one by the way all the pandas
are shipping out and they're coming in
these beautiful boxes we have tons of
Panda
so neat and this is the latest panda
injection molded case technology you're
gonna be getting a pretty printed pan up
boxing right you guys that well who's
that guy Bryan Bryan comedian who's
funny man you just get a box $10 um oh
yeah so this is gonna be our new URL
it's not live yet this is the official
UPC for the Panda it's order one today
or if you haven't gotten yours yet
you've already ordered it we're gonna be
shipping it out in a beautiful cardboard
box how crazy these alright so let's
open one of these up let's see if this
is a 3d printed one or an injection
molder this is a 3d printed one we can
look inside we can see panda Panda right
actually great packaging though right
how much to autograph the box that's 20
that's a 3d printed one let's see if we
can find an injection molded one the box
is a little hard to open but that's good
oh yeah look at this injection molded
panda so how to walk guys Panda I'll
play for tonight
I'll beat anyone at age of empires
anyone wants to bet me $100
vampires let's go alright so this is an
injection-molded panda these are still
pretty rare we've run into a few
manufacturing difficulties with them oh
so you all can be getting pretty pretty
pandas this is a 3d printed panda what
is the age of empire is my parents best
game in history compares to browse
conquerors exposure um but yes that's an
injection-molded panda that's a 3d
printed panda
order today get your panda we'll listen
to the Panda song that sounds good no
these people working distracting enough
but well we are gonna do is go
downstairs and look at bags and bags of
pens Oh what's open
over here crazy yo guys let me tell you
what else
pandas are indestructible look at this
no damage
beautiful panda I did break one when I
threw it at the floor really really hard
like Logan power plates but for the most
part they're pretty indestructible let's
just go downstairs we'll say hi to Ed
you real fast and we will show you this
huge box that pandas came in guys pandas
are back in stock go right now to shop
comedy i buy your panda and we will ship
it out on Thursday hey you wanna say out
of the scope ease what I want to say is
go visa to show them all the pandas well
we got lots of pandas y'all show you
guys at the inside of the Panda looks
like check this out that's a pan pandas
red boards black bass board
look at that panda beautiful 3d printed
founders are totally limited edition
Eddie's right over here disassembling
panda he's assembling great panda Panda
there's a great fan of top carrier board
for our u-blox module
there are three ready to go all right
guys thank you for joining come get the
hottest panda in the game uh hottest
panda in the game check out I got the
favorite hoodie alright um come get the
hottest pan in the game right now shop
comedy I go by your pandas they will all
ship out what's that on Thursday right
15th yeah guys these odd scobie's we
never support Subaru no no you can
support Subaru